stephencovey.com 2019-07-04

# Privacy Policy

1\. Purpose of This Privacy Notice

This privacy notice describes how Franklin Covey collects and processes your personal data through your use of this website and the services on it, including any data you may provide.

This website is not intended to be used by children; Franklin Covey does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children.

It is important that you read this privacy notice, together with any other privacy notice or fair processing notice provided when personal data is collected or processed, so that you are fully aware of how your data is used. This privacy notice is supplemental to any other notice and is not intended to override.    

**Controller**

Franklin Covey is comprised of several different legal entities, details of which are available at: <https://www.franklincovey.com/About/global-offices.html>.  This privacy notice is issued on behalf of Franklin Covey Co. Reference to "Franklin Covey," "we," "us," or "our" in this privacy notice implies Franklin Covey Co., who is responsible for processing your data. Unless otherwise stated, Franklin Covey Co. is the controller of this website.

Franklin Covey’s data privacy manager will respond to questions regarding this privacy notice. If you have any questions about this privacy notice, including any requests to exercise your legal rights, please contact the data privacy manager using the details provided below: 

**Contact Information**

Legal Entity:       Franklin Covey Co.

Data Privacy Manager: Blaine Carter

Email Address:   [privacy@franklincovey.com](mailto:privacy@franklincovey.com)      

Postal Address:  2200 W Parkway Blvd, Salt Lake City, UT 84119, United States   

The contact for our EU Representative: 

Legal Entity:       Franklin Covey Europe Ltd      

Data Privacy Manager: Stephen Asker      

Email Address:   [privacy@franklincovey.co.uk](mailto:privacy@franklincovey.co.uk)        

Postal Address:  Ground Floor Blenheim Court, 19 George Street, Banbury, Oxfordshire OX16 5BH, United Kingdom    

You have the right to file a complaint at any time with the Information Commissioner's Office (ICO), the supervisory authority for data protection issues. However, we would appreciate the opportunity to resolve your concerns before you approach the ICO, so please consider contacting us first.   

**Changes to the Privacy Notice and Request for Current Data**

This Privacy Notice was last updated on May 11th, 2018

It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. Please notify us of any changes to your personal information during your relationship with us.

**Third-Party Links**

This website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins, and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites, and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy notice of every website you visit.
